看呐 我们的小戴夫正在泡妞
Look at our little Dave rose, making friends.
跟你赌五块钱 他正在说
Bet you 5 bucks he's telling her about the time
他横穿密西根大街救小狗的事
he ran across Michigan Ave. to save that puppy.
不可能 他肯定在讲他高中那次
No way. He's telling the story from high school where he
救球然后跑回来着地得分的故事
picked up that fumble and ran it back for a touchdown...
蹦! 接住了橄榄球 来啦 得分啦~
And boom! Football. There it is. Pay up, playa.
等等 那是只小狗
Hold up. That's a puppy dog.
哦!
Oh!
希望那是橄榄球的故事吧
Let's hope it was a football,
否则就是我们没有听到
or else we have not heard
英雄救狗的完整版
the complete story about the puppy.
哇
Whoa.
兄弟 那个妞对你很有意思啊
Dude, that girl's super into you, man.
我知道 我知道
I know, I know.
她甚至就像
She even liked my reenactment
"魔域奇兵"第一个场景的再现
of the first scene of "Temple of Doom."
-啊 "毁灭战士" -太形象了
- Ah. "Doom." - It's the go-to move. Of course.
哦 嘿 同志们 这是安德烈娅
Oh, hey, guys, this is Andrea.
事实上 人家叫安卓拉
Actually, it's Un-drea.
-安卓拉 -安卓拉
-Un-drea. -Un-drea.
好吧 我是马克斯 这是布雷德
Okay. Well, I am Max, this is Brade.
这是戴夫 你知道的
Of course you know Dave.
你的朋友也很有趣啊
Your friends are so funny.
-我去拿我的钱包 -好的
-I'm gonna grab my purse. -Okay.
哪也别去哦
Don't go anywhere.
-嘣! -哦!
-Boop! -Oh!
我知道 她有点傻 但是很辣 是不是?
I mean, she's totally lame but super hot, right?
是啊 你可真得好好享受
Yeah, you should totally boop that.
耶 我还没做好开始一段新感情的准备
Yeah, not really ready for a relationship.
-没有? -嘿 尼古拉斯 斯巴克斯
- No? - Hey, Nicholas Sparks,
没人在意你俩的关系
no one's talking about a relationship.
我是说把弗兰基 菲德拉带回家
I'm talking about taking Frankie Fedora home,
搞点恶心事 然后再不要联系她了
doing some weird stuff, and never calling her again.
我回来啦!
I'm back!
哇! 你可真嗨啊
Whoa! You are a gosh-darn delight!
戴夫 我们走吧
Dave, let's get out of here.
唔... 好吧
Um... okay.
好的 啵! 哦!
Okay. Boop! Oh!
我真的不能理解这种需要
I do not understand people that feel the need
通过摸别人来表达感情的人的心理
to express themselves through touching.
我懂的 好吧? 好了 我走了
I know, right? All right, I'm out.
啊! 停! 别碰我~
Aah! Stop! Can't touch this.
哦 好了 回见了 老兄
Ohh. All right, I'll see you, buddy.
幸福终点站
第一季第二集
==深影字幕组==
我了个擦
What the hell?
寻觅室友吗，快来和我一起快乐的玩耍吧！
给我
Give me that.
怎么了? 赚的钱可以补贴我的小店
What? I could use the extra cash for the store,
所以找个新室友应该是个好主意
and I decided a roommate might be a good idea.
你准备被抓去卖成老白奴吗?
Are you trying to get sold into white slavery?
简 这张照片看上去很Q嘛
Jane, it's a cute picture.
哦 老天 我是不是露点了?
Oh, my God. Is that side boob?
哦 上帝 这...
Oh, my God. It...
不 不 不 不 只是树叶子了
No. No, no, no. It's just leaves.
随便啦 我会找一个又酷又有趣的室友
Whatever. I'll find someone cool and fun,
会好的
and it'll be okay.
宝贝...这是个重大决定 对吧?
Honey... This is a big decision, okay?
你有个坏习惯
And... and you have a terrible habit
总是能看到人们身上的优点
of always seeing the good in people.
我不觉得那是个坏毛病啊
Not sure that's a bad habit.
好吧 我的意思是
Okay, what I'm trying to say is that
你看人不准
you're not the best judge of character.
太不可思议了 哦 戴夫
That's crazy. Oh, Dave.
这是扎恩 他刚刚搬过来
This is Zane. He just moved into the building.
他串门拉领里关系
He's introducing himself to all the neighbors.
法律上 我必须这么做
Legally, I have to.
你要不要我帮你找个室友
Would you like me to help you find a roommate?
简 我自己可以处理
Jane, I can handle this.
我可以找一个...
I can make one...
-简 -好吧
-Jane. -Okay.
兄弟 拦球啊
Dude, stop him.
挺下来 不要... 老兄!
Stop. Don't... dude!
别看球了!
No football!
好不好? 来嘛 马克斯
Okay? Come on, Max.
我们一起去农贸市场转转
Let's go to the farmers' market.
洛杉矶展会有一场时装秀
There's a trunk show at Shoe-La-La,
然后我们可以一起吃早午餐
and then we can brunch it up!
你知道什么听上去更吸引人吗?
You know what sounds more fun?
穿着湿衣服 看"辛德勒的名单"
Being in wet clothes and watching "Schindler's List."
你真是有史上最烂的同志老公
You're the worst gay husband ever.
哦 小妞 这只手上可没带戒指哦
Oh, I don't see no ring on this finger, girl.
简在干嘛?
What's Jane doing?
现在是周末 她放松在
It's the weekend. She's relaxing.
再高一点... 这样会不会更容易
Just a pitch... wouldn't it be easier
找到这些储物箱 如果把他们放在货架里?
to find these stackables if they were in the shelving section?
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
这个女人是在质疑商店商品的摆放
Is this woman questioning the organization of a store
这些储物箱可都是帮人们整理东西的
whose sole purpose is to help people organize?
是的
Yes.
好吧 无聊透顶的足球比赛
Fine. Stupid football.
喔! 昨天晚上打了炮的把手举起来
Whoo! Raise your hand if you got laid last night.
真的吗?
Really?
耶 我们在烤披萨的时候
Yeah, Jane gets stupid horny
简居然欲火焚身了
when we use our pizza stone.
我昨天是和我的过敏科医生医生一起过夜的
I slept with my allergist.
一个茫然的大学生
Confused college student.
啊 我不想撒谎 你们差不多都抢了我的风头
Ugh. I'm not gonna lie. You guys are kinda stealing my thunder.
嘿 别这样戴夫 行行好吧
Hey, no Dave, good for you.
你还准备见她吗?
Are you gonna see her again?
我不知道 她在床上带软毡帽
I don't know. She wore a fedora in bed.
也许我可以叫她...
I probably should call her...
别 千万别说出来
No. Mnh-mnh.
别别别 这样就破坏了一夜情第一定律了
Mnh-mnh. That is breaking the first rule of one night stands.
好吧 我不想当坏人
Well, I don't wanna be a bad guy,
还是给她打个电话吧
so just gonna give her a call.
要是我就不会给她打电话 别打
I wouldn't call her. No. No.
别打啊 不 她会缠着你的
Don't do it. Mnh-mnh. She's gonna pick up.
哇! 嘿 安德烈娅
Whoa! Hey. Andrea.
-看吧 -安卓拉 对不起啦
-There it is. -Un-drea. Sorry.
我打电话想跟你说声谢谢
I was just calling to say thank you
对昨天晚上的事... 早餐
for last night. It... Breakfast.
不
No.
不 别啊...
No. Um...
好的 可以 嗯 我可以...
Okay. Sure. Yeah, I can...
十五分钟之内赶到
be there in 15 minutes.
不啊
No!
童鞋们 笑一个 我一个小时就回来
Make the face. Guys, relax. It's just an hour.
我马上回来 然后跟你们一起看比赛
I'll be back. We'll be watching football...
不醉不归!
And drinking heavily!
戴夫 你去哪了?
Dave, where have you been?
同志们 我记不清楚了
Guys, it's all a blur.
我们边吃法式薄饼边走到湖旁
We went to eat crepes, which led to a walk by the lake.
然后我们去了她的公寓
After that, we went to her apartment
一起喂她的小鸟
to feed her bird.
没错 同志们 她真的养了一只小鸟
That's right, guys. She's got a bird!
然后我们一起看了她所有的跳舞视频
Then we watched all of her dance videos
从高中到大学的 很明显
from high school through college because apparently
她要去参加卡傻的世界巡回演唱会面试
she's auditioning for Keesha's world tour.
是钱傻
It's Kesha.
然后我们又去了自然博物馆
Then we went down to the Field Museum
她要我买了张两年期会员卡
where she convinced me to buy a joint membership
因为这样就可以免费停车了
for two years because you get free parking.
见鬼 戴夫 你陷到妞沙里去了
Damn, Dave. You are stuck in chick-sand.
-什么鬼东西 -嗯 是流沙
-What is that? -It's, uh, it's quicksand,
我用"妞"代替了"流"
except I replaced the "quick" with "chick."
算了吧 老兄 别瞎掰了
Come on, man. You're better than that.
同志们 我应该怎么做?
Guys, what am I gonna do?
听着 如果你还想见她的话直接跟她说好了
Look, if you don't wanna see her again, you just tell her.
成熟点 好好跟她谈一下
Be an adult and have the conversation.
别啊 别啊 太恶心了 -是额 千万别谈
-No. No, conversation sucks. -Yeah, right. Nope!
不 你是对的 我是个成年人了
No. You're right. I am an adult,
那么...我就应该用成年人的方式
and... and I'm gonna handle this
来处理这件事
like an adult.
我先去洗个澡 然后去找她
I'm gonna take a shower, and I'm gonna march myself down there,
我们是应该好好谈谈
and we're gonna have a conversation.
我看出来了 你是怎么把
I see how you got from
"流沙"变成"妞沙"的 你真是个傻逼
"quicksand" to "chick-sand." You're an idiot.
我喜欢你
I love you.
童鞋们!~
Guys!
嘿 这是萨曼塔 她可能成为我的新室友
Hey! This is Samantha. She might be my new roommate.
嘿 嗨~
Hey. Hi.
-我们再联系 -好的
-We'll be in touch. -Yes.
-好的 拜拜 -拜~
- Okay, great. Bye. - Bye.
她看起来棒极了! 她的头发真是美呆了
Doesn't she seem great? Her hair is amazing.
是啊 她的头发上面有社保号
Yeah. Does her hair have a social security number
让你能知道她的信誉吗 还有她的介绍信呢?
you can run a credit check on? Or how about her references?
我是说 她一个月收入多少?
I mean, how much money does she make?
你真的了解她吗?
What do you really know about her?
她喜欢吸血鬼小说和碧昂丝?
She likes vampire books and Beyonc?
你知道吗
You know,
我在塔拉哈西有一个十三岁的小侄子
I have a 13-year-old cousin in Tallahassee
想离家出走
that's thinking about running away from home.
-对你来说可能是个合格的室友 -好吧
- Maybe he'd make a good roommate for you. - Okay.
我们都得跟你选的室友出去玩 阿历
Now we're all gonna have to hang out with whoever you choose, Al,
所以怎么不选个好玩的人捏
so why don't you pick someone fun,
像是个战斗飞行员 或者是斯科奇 皮彭
like a fighter pilot or Scottie Pippen?
哦 你知道你应该选谁吗? 一个货真价实的钙男
Oh, you know who you should get? Is a real gay guy.
哇
Whoa.
算了吧 你是个喜欢男人的直男
Come on. You're a straight dude who likes dudes.
我想要一个可以和我一起看肥皂剧的钙男
I want a gay who will watch house flipping shows with me
能柏拉图式的抚摸人家的咪咪
and grab my boobs in a platonic way.
这么说你想找个刻板形象的张扬的狗血的
So you want a stereotypically flamboyant, cartoonish
"欲望都市"式的弯男？这太冒犯人了
"Sex and the City" gay? That's offensive.
心之所系，我之所想
The heart wants what the heart wants.
听着 你只跟戴夫和我住过
Look, you've only ever lived with Dave and me,
做这个决定有很多因素要考虑进去
and a lot goes into making this decision.
好吧 我想我还没有考虑好
Well, I guess I didn't totally think about all of that.
但是我考虑好了 我看人很准的
But I did. Okay, and judging people comes so easy for me,
这就是为什么你得要我帮助你的原因
which is why you should let me help you.
是的 好吧 你可以帮忙 但是别越界
Okay. Fine. You can help, but you're not gonna come in
帮我决定每件事 把你那套都强加在我身上
and take over everything and get all "Jane" on me, are you?
当然不会了
Of course not.
我找到个很棒的室友
I've got some great roommate choices.
贝卡 她是个海洋生物学家
Like a Becca. She's a marine biologist
和公证人 也就是说她可以教你认浮游生物
and notary public, which means she can teach you about plankton
还可以为签署重要文件做公证人
and also witness the signing of important documents.
听起来这不错
Sounds like such fun!
我就知道
I know.
但是我现在不能这么做 简
But I can't do this right now, Jane.
好啦 好啦 杰西卡怎么样?
Okay, okay, how about Jessica?
她是个恐旷症患者和一个素食主义者
I mean, she's an agoraphobic and a vegan,
这就意味着她绝对不会离开自己的房间
which means she will never leave her room
或者是偷吃你的奶酪 你爱你的奶酪嘛!~
or eat your cheese. You love your cheese!
嘿 你们觉得这条裙子...怎么样?
Hey, what do you guys think of this... dress?
没人在意
And no one cares.
哟 彭妮
Yo, Penny.
小妞 你看起来这是秀色可餐!
Girl! That dress looks delish!
是什么让你这么美!~~~~~~~~~
What? Things that make you go mmm!
嗨
Hi.
阿里嘎多 马克斯 这位好心的先生是?
Gracias. Max, who is this fine man?
彭妮 这是德瑞克
Penny, I'd like you to meet Derrick.
我们去年一起在一个同志垒球队打球
We played on a gay softball team together last year.
我觉得你们会相处得很好的
I thought you guys might get along.
P.S....四环球(垒球用语)
P.S.... Four balls
不是散步 是个宴会 什么? 抓马!
isn't just a walk. It's a party. What? Drama!
我可以碰碰你的咪咪吗? 就在这~
Can I touch your ta-tas? Get in there.
-啊! 啊! -哦 老天啊 (==)
-Aah! Aah! -Oh, my God.
哦 我对你一见如故啊
I feel like I've known you so long.
哦 老天啊 我已经开始想你了
Oh, my God. I already miss you.
哦 上帝 我们是在战斗吗?
Oh, my God. Are we in a fight?
-不 我去帮你拿配饰 好吗? -去吧
- No. I'm gonna get you accessories, okay? - Get out of here, you.
拜 回头见
Bye. All right. See you soon.
够GAY吗 彭?
Gay enough for you, Pen?
小荡妇 快来扶我起来!
Slut! Come help me out of this split!
他正是我梦寐以求的钙男
He's the gay of my dreams.
-戴夫还会和我们见面吗? -我也不知道
-Is Dave still meeting us? -I don't know.
自从两天前他去找安卓拉谈话
I haven't seen him since he went
以后我就再也没见过他
<i>to have the conversation with Un-drea two days ago.</i>
喔 等 等 等等 等等等
Ooh, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
噢
Oh.
他头上戴着什么?
What is he wearing on his head?
再见 小亲亲
Bye, Moo-Moo.
再见 小笨蛋
Au revoir, doodle bug.
伙计们 我有大麻烦了
Guys... I'm in serious trouble.
噢 怎么了 小亲亲?
Aw, what happened, Moo-Moo?
好吧 我去找她谈话
Well, I went to have the conversation,
但是在我开口以前
but before I could say anything,
她就开始向我倒苦水
she launched into this whole thing
她说能遇到像我这样的好男人真的是太好了
about how great it is to finally meet a good guy
还有她前男友是怎么偷她爸爸的钱
and about how her last boyfriend stole from her dad
然后又和她表妹偷情 所以...我开不了口
and had sex with her cousin, so... I couldn't do it.
兄弟 你完全偏离了重点
Dude, you're missing the point.
她有一个有钱的老爸和一个淫荡的表妹
She's got a rich dad and slutty cousins.
告诉你 谈话真的很难
Told you, bro. Conversation's hard.
拜托 我已经很久没有玩过什么感情游戏了
Guys, I've been out of the game too long.
我该怎么做?
What do I do?
第一点 不要再把感情称为"游戏"
First off, stop calling it "the game."
我想你该像学学怎么"慢慢淡化"
I think you should go with the Peter-out.
噢！我喜欢慢慢淡化
Ooh! I love the Peter-out.
不要定期的约她出来 要时不时的改变计划
Stop calling her regularly. Change your plans
第二点也是最后一点
at the last second.
周末晚上不要和她出来约会
Never go out with her on a weekend night.
这样持续一段时间
Couple of days,
你们的感情就会...慢慢淡化
things will just... Peter out.
根本用不着什么谈话
No conversation.
你下一次约她是什么时候?
When's the next time you're seeing her?
星期六晚上
Saturday night.
很好 告诉她 约会改到星期三了
Perfect. Text her. Change it to Wednesday,
一个星期中最不性感的一天
the least sexy night of the week.
我很吃惊你把计划改到今晚
I was surprised you decided to switch plans to tonight.
我没想到我们已经发展到这一步了
<i>I didn't know we were quite there yet.</i>
我周六有点事要忙
My Saturdays are getting kinda booked,
等等... 发展到哪一步?
<i>but... wait. Where yet?</i>
生日快乐！
Happy Birthday!
今天是你的生日
It's your birthday.
大家 这就是戴夫！
Everybody, everybody, this is Dave!
嗨 戴夫
Hi, Dave!
戴夫 这是我的祖母 内莉
Dave, this is my grandma Nellie.
噢 你好 很高兴认识你
Oh, hi. Nice to meet you.
噗！噢！
Boop! Oh!
我想来点威士忌 你要吗?
I'm gonna get a scotch. You want a scotch?
噢！你太可爱了！
Oh! You're so cute!
简 你在这干嘛?
Jane, what are you doing here?
恩 你一直没有告诉我你最喜欢谁
Well, you never got back to me on who you liked,
所以我选出了十个最佳室友候选人
so I picked the ten best roommate candidates
所以我把他们请来参加一个家庭招待会
and invited them over for a little open house.
什么?什么时候?
What? When?
- 现在 - 现在?
- Right now. - Right now?
对 我得赶紧准备派对
Yep. So I'm gonna finish getting ready.
你呢 赶紧洗澡换衣服
You should probably shower, change, you know,
穿你喜欢的  但是我帮你挑好了一件
wear whatever you like, but I laid out
非常好看的 就放在你床上 所以就穿那件
a really cute suggestion on your bed, so wear that.
那天是她的生日?
It was her birthday?
很明显 是的
Yeah. Apparently,
某天她在和我打炮的时候告诉我的
she told me while we were having sex the other night.
我以为她应该是在想让我干她
I just thought she was telling me to do her
就像是她快要过生日一样
like it was her birthday...
谁知道下个礼拜三真是她生日 - 你正面临真正的妞沙
Next Wednesday. You're in serious chick-sand.
- 那不是一个词 - 我创造的
Not a word. I'm making it one.
你不能自己造词
Can't just make words.
它就是 我正在申请把它写进字典里
It is. I submitted it to the dictionary.
- 得到回复了吗? - 几乎
- You hear back? - Almost.
你已经回复了?
You almost heard back?
伙计们 我需要帮忙 拜托
Guys, I need a little help here, please.
你没事 我是说 你没有跟她回家对吗?
You're fine. I mean, you didn't go home with her, did you?
- 我去 - 拜托 生日炮?
No. Dude. Birthday sex?
你看 慢慢淡化这招根本就没有用好不好
Look, petering out is not working, all right?
很明显 我已经淡化了两次半了
Apparently, I petered in two and a half times.
那半次是什么意思?
What's the half?
我也不知道 她说那好像是法国人的什么玩法
I don't know. She said it was like a French thing.
不要紧张 你只要尽情的享乐
Don't panic. Just gotta crank it up a notch.
让她快速的发现你就不是块
Make this chick realize really quickly
做男朋友的料
that you are not boyfriend material.
拜托 我很明显就是块当男朋友的料好不?
Dude, I am awesome boyfriend material, okay?
我喜欢长途步行 我喜欢划桨...
I like long walks. I like puddles...
跳进又跳出
jumping in and jumping out.
我喜欢听那些有关练瑜伽的时候
I like listening to really long stories
谁坐到了谁的身边这种长故事 我惨了
about who sat next to who at yoga. I'm in trouble.
不 你一点也不惨
Look, you're not in trouble.
听我的 赶快就可以结束这一切
Do what I say, and by the end of one horrible date,
你只要在她面前表现出你的不可靠
she'll break up with you. You just gotta show her
吝啬 还有古怪 她一定会和你分手
that you're unreliable and cheap and weird.
等等 兄弟 听上去怎么这么像
Wait, dude. That sounds like
一部丹麦的厨师电影里面的场景
the plot of a Dane cook movie.
不 但是应该的，因为就是有那么棒
No, but it should be. It is that awesome.
扯吧你
Yeah.
抱歉 抱歉 我迟到了这么久
I know. I know. I'm so late.
看 我没有买手表
See, I don't own a watch
因为我想不通为什么
because what is time anyway
我们的时间要被这种机械给束缚住?
but a man-made shackle?
你说的这些很像
That is almost literally
我在高中年刊上的写的一句话
my high school yearbook quote verbatim.
我讨厌匆忙的人生
I hate rushing places!
我们真是灵魂伴侣！噢！
Soul mates! Oh!
来吧
Come on!
阿历 这是切尔西
Al, this is Chelsea.
她从新泽西州来 从事金融工作
She's from New Jersey. She works in Finance,
她还是国家公共电台的志愿者
and she's a volunteer for NPR.
你是新泽西人?
You're from New Jersey?
那你肯定喜欢看"真实主妇"这个节目哦
That is totally the best "Real Housewives,"
但是我有点为丹尼尔担心
but I am legitimately worried about Danielle.
噢 我没有买电视
Oh. I don't own a TV.
那你晚上都干些什么?
What... do you do at night?
- 写日记 - 一整晚?
I journal. All night?
我感觉这一屋子的姑娘都是jane的翻版
I feel like all these girls look like Jane.
是的 就像她们把特瑞伯奇的商场屋顶给拿到
Yep, it's like they took the roof off a Tory Burch store
- 这间空房子里来了- 特瑞 伯奇是什么
- and emptied it into this apartment. - What's Tory Burch?
她是 恩 一个设计师
She's, uh, she's a designer.
有一点学院风 时髦又带一点...
It's kinda preppy, boho-chic meets upt...
你确定你是个同志?
<i>Are you sure you're gay?
你确定你不是同志?
Are you sure you're not gay?</i>
- 嘿 骚货们 - 干嘛?
<i>Hey, sluts. What?</i>
德瑞克和我刚从
Derrick and I just came
三家分开的农民市场回来
from three separate farmers' markets.
好消息...祖传的西红柿是新的甜菜
Announcement... heirloom tomatoes are the new beets.
什么?D-r-a-m-a 亮瞎！ 亮瞎！
<i>What? D-r-a-m-a. Drama! Drama!</i>
就这样 好 为了素食主义者
Right there. Yep, for veggies.
我认识他吗?
Do I know that guy?
他是我新的好朋友 德瑞克
Oh, that's my new B.F.F., Derrick.
彭妮 阿卡德！
Penny Arcade!
快来和我一起嘲笑这个沙发！
Come over here and help me mock this couch!
他是不是赞翻天了
Isn't he amah-zing?
我真的为你高兴 凯西 格林芬
I'm very happy for you, Kathy Griffin.
谁是凯西 格林芬?
Who's Kathy Griffin?
好吧 原来你不是同志啊
Okay, so you're not gay.
额 我没带现金出门
Yeah, I don't have any cash,
银行，也就是我爹妈，刚给我打了电话
and the bank just called, a.k.a. my parents.
而且很明显 我信用卡已经刷爆了
And apparently I maxed out my credit card
完全没有办法 所以
breeding boa constrictors, so...
够了 停下来
Okay, stop right there.
我很欣赏...你对我直说了
I love... that you can admit that.
噢
Oh.
我很乐意付账
I'm happy to pay.
好的 你当然愿意买单 你真好
Okay. Of course you'd wanna do that. That's great.
当然
I do.
好吧 那个...
Okay, so... Yeah.
我有一个很好的故事 有点疯狂
I have the best story. This is insanity.
我们去温戈饭店用早午餐 那里的服务员
We're at Ungo having brunch, and the waiter...
哦 我的神呐 打鼾
Oh, my God. Snore.
讨厌 你会讲故事吗?还是我来说吧
Jeez, skank. Have you ever told a story? I'll take it from here.
好 说到 那个可爱的服务员走过来对吗?
Okay, cut to... cute waiter walks up, right?
这位露胸罩的饥渴女
And little miss push-up bra is so eager
迫不及待的想去调戏那个服务生
to flirt with him...
基本上我告诉那个服务员
Basically, I said to the waiter...
...她把她的炒蛋全喷在了他的裤子上
...that she spits up her scrambled eggs on his pants.
怎样?你们别笑喷了 我很想对她说
What? I'm like, say it, don't spray it,
你这个蠢透了的贱人
you stupid clumsy bitch.
- 你真是个蠢透了的贱人 - 真是蠢透了
- You're such a clumsy bitch. - You are a clumsy bitch.
噢 天呐 噢！
Ahh! Oh, my God. Ohh!
你说得对 他确实赞翻天了
<i>You're right, Pen, he is amah-zing.</i>
是 没错 他真是太搞笑了
Yeah. Yeah. He's hilarious.
阿历 这是特瑞西
Al, this is Trish.
她去年登上了乞力马扎罗山
She summitted Mount Kilimanjaro last year.
他们叫他"基利"对吗?
They call it "Killy," right?
而且她会做吊床
<i>And she makes hammocks.</i>
你们两个肯定谈得来
So you guys have a lot in common.
我 很抱歉 特瑞西 你看上去很好 真的
I'm... sorry, Trish. You seem great, really,
可是我已经找到室友了
but I've already found a roommate.
哦！没关系
Oh! Okay.
- 哦 抱歉 - 谢谢 简
Eek. Sorry. Thank you, Jane.
那...你选的室友是?
<i>So... Who did we choose?</i>
我的第一选择是...萨曼塔 红头发的那个
My first choice... Samantha, with the red hair.
我不明白 我才向你介绍了
I don't understand. I just introduced you
是个更优秀的女孩做室友
to ten other girls who would make way better roommates.
是啊 那是为了你 好吗?
<i>Yeah, for you, okay?
但是我想要一个有个性的室友
But I want someone cool.</i>
我不在乎她们是不是有什么好工作
I-I don't care if they "look good on paper"
或者有什么好的文化背景
or "have great references"
或者爬没爬过乞力马扎罗山
or "climbed Mount Kilimajoojoo."
你为什么把它们都加上引号?
Why are you putting everything in air quotes?
因为这就是我 很抱歉
'Cause that's who I am, and I'm sorry
我不想和这些无聊的女人住在一起
if I don't wanna live with any of these boring, lame girls.
妈呀.- 好戏上演!!!!!
Ohh...- drama!!!!
兄弟 都不管用
Bro, nothing is working.
我想这个女人肯定是爱上我了
I think this crazy chick is falling in love with me.
我不想伤害她
I do not wanna crush her,
就像我不久前被甩时那样伤心 懂?
being that I have recently been crushed, all right?
这样一点都不好玩 我该怎么办?
It is not fun.  What do I do?
你就这样好了 在她从洗手间回来以前
This is what you do. Before she gets back from the bathroom,
你双腿跪地 让后向上帝祈祷
you get down on your knees and you pray to God
祈祷他赶紧让饭店爆炸
that the restaurant explodes.
扮演上帝?有没有搞错?这就是你想的办法?
Act of God? Really, man? That's the best you've got?
啊！啊！
Aah! Aah!
噢！天呐！我得到那份工作了！
Oh, my God! I got the job!
以后我就是钱傻的欧洲之旅的替补伴舞了！
I'm gonna be a backup dancer for KeSha's European Tour!
我星期四就走！
I leave Thursday!
噢 真是太感谢你了！
Oh, my gosh. Thank you so much!
兄弟 饭店的确爆炸了
Dude, the restaurant just exploded.
噢 天呐 那我们两怎么办?
Oh, God, what's gonna happen to us?
噢 你不该总想着我们 不 不 你要...
Oh, you can't think about us. No, no, you just...
你要去做你想做的 知道吗?
<i>You just gotta do you, you know?</i>
你...你生命中不能没有舞蹈
You... you can't separate the dancer from the dance.
噢 我的天 你真的是太好了 么么
Oh, my God. You are amazing, Moo-Moo.
噢
Oh.
你先 小笨蛋
After you, doodle bug.
这是我有过的最美好的一次约会...
This has been the best date I ever...
啊！
Aah!
噢！啊...安德烈娅 你没事吧?
Ohh! Uh... Andrea, are you okay?
安卓拉 安卓拉 安卓拉 你还好吗?
Un-drea. Un-drea, Un-drea, are you okay?
她被一个骑自行车的邮递员给撞了?
She got hit by a bike messenger?
- 是的 - 闭嘴
Of course she did. Shut up!
去年万圣节我还被
I got hit by a cop
一个开着赛格威的巡警给撞了
on a Segway last Halloween.
恩 我当时除了一条海豚短裤
Ugh. I was wearing nothing
和一个绿色毛皮围巾 其他什么也没穿
but dolphin shorts and a feather green boa.
我想把他的帽子偷过来
I tried to steal his hat.
切换场景 卡博的周末
Cut to... Weekend in Cabo.
因为我长胖了 他回到他那个笨蛋老婆那去
Then he went back to his "dumb wife" because I'm fat.
你是谁来着?
Who... are you again?
啊 是 德罗克 我超爱他 来
Ah, it's D-Rock. I love him. Come here. Ow.
戴夫 有什么我可以帮的上忙的吗?
Dave, let me know if there's anything I can do to help.
比如说 我可以打电话给她 或者...
You know, like maybe I could call her or...
彭妮丫头 拜托 这没你事好吗?
Penny Loafer, please, this is not about you, okay?
戴夫 你需要的是
Dave, what you need, right?
新裤子和减肥
Are new pants, a couple of shake weights,
以及一个你我之间的俄式泡沫吧狂欢夜
and a night out at a Russian foam club with me.
怎么样?跟哥混
Okay? Moi truly.
他实际上什么都不需要
Yeah, he literally needs none of those things.
好了 往那 停下
All right, and there and off.
老兄 想想好的地方
Dude, look at the bright side.
你逃出来了 她周四不久去欧洲了么?
You're out. I mean, she's going to Europe on Thursday, right?
她不去 骨折了你怎么跳
No. She's not. You can't dance with a broken femur.
一针见血
Debatable.
而且她接下来两个月都要打石膏
And because she's gonna be in a cast for the next eight weeks,
住六楼还没电梯
and because she lives in a 6-story walk-up,
我好同情她
and I feel so bad about what happened that...
她要搬来住了是吗- 好戏上演!!
She's moving in, isn't she?-drama!!
我俩是舍友真好
I'm so glad that we're roommates.
我向你保证简的那些书呆子女人
I guarantee you none of Jane's nerdy choices
一点也比不上
would have ever gotten me
这件美呆了的迈克尔 斯达斯小背心
this awesome Michael Stars tank top.
你真辣 哦 你不介意
You look hot. Oh, hey, do you mind
我再装条网线吧?
if I get another D.S.L. line installed
可能会遮掉点光
and maybe black out a couple of these windows?
当然 我猜
Sure... I guess.
哦
Oh.
嗨 简 你想知道我舍友怎么样
Hi, Jane. If you're wondering how my new roommate is,
她酷毙了
she's awesome.
我只是想告诉你很高兴你把一切都搞定了
I just called to say that I'm glad it all worked out for you,
我真喜欢你的小背心
and I really like that tank top on you.
等等 你怎么知道我穿啥?
Wait. How do you know what I'm wearing?
你酷毙的萨曼塔靠偷拍可爱室友的
Your awesome Samantha makes a living by moving in
生活为生
with cute girls, setting up webcams,
-人们付钱去看 -哦 我的天!
- and charging people to watch. - Oh, my God!
怪不得她昨天舔棒冰
That's why she wanted to eat popsicles
还有玩奶油芝士大战
and have a cream cheese fight yesterday.
哦 是 那是很受欢迎的一段
Oh, yeah. That's a popular one.
等等 你哪里找到的?
Wait. How did you find this?
我的天
Oh, my God. I know.
等等 你哪里找到的?
Wait. How did you find this?
嗯 我看其他东西的时候突然跳出来的
Uh... just a pop-up on another thing I was looking at.
什么东西?
What other thing?
一个 烹饪博客?
A... cooking blog?
体育?
Sports?
太疯狂了
This is so crazy.
我以为萨曼塔是个酷女孩 你知道吗?
I mean, I thought Samantha was a cool girl, you know?
会不会搞错了?
Is there any way that this is a mistake?
嗨 真棒 你姐姐也在
Hey, great. Your sister's here.
你们想一起玩枕头大战还是剃下腿毛?
Do you guys wanna have a pillow fight or shave your legs together?
要我搞定吗?
Do you want me to handle this?
不 我想一起来
No. I think we should do this together.
-哦!上 阿历克斯-小背心不错
- Oh! Go, Alex. - Cute "t"-tops.
这个直接就跳出来了?
So this just popped up on the computer?
你们干嘛老问这个?
Why do you people keep asking me that?
我又管不了网 好不好
I don't control the Internet, all right?
嗨 戴夫 怎么样了?
Hey, Dave. How's it going?
越来越好了 彭
It's going great, Pen.
一个疯女人和一只傻鸟就
I've got a crazy girl and a douche bird
住在我的房间里 多亏了这两个笨蛋
living in my room thanks to these two idiots.
你们还有没有更好的办法?
You guys got any more advice for me?
没 你有个正式的女友了
Nothin'. You got a serious girlfriend now.
兄弟 你陷到妞沙里了
You drowned, bro, in chick-sand.
我喜欢这词我就用了
I like it and I'm taking credit for it.
德瑞克想一起吃早午餐
Derrick wants to go to another brunch.
就像一个人到底能吃多少
It's, like, how many egg white frittatas
菜肉煎蛋饼? - 一次六个
can a person eat? Six in one sitting.
但我以为你爱德罗克
But I thought you loved D-Rock.
我爱! 不 实际上我不爱
I do! No, you know what? I don't. Okay?
我以为我想要
I thought that I wanted
这种典型的夸张型的刻板同志 但太过了
this offensively stereotypical gay guy, but it's too much.
我觉得他破坏了我们的关系
I mean, I feel like it messes with the group dynamic.
是的 彭 因为我们已经有
It does, Pen, 'cause our group already has
一个典型的夸张型同志
an offensively stereotypical gay guy.
女神嘎嘎演唱会第一排的票子 小贱人们!
Front row tickets to Gaga, bitches!
我那个巨无霸美甲师
My disgustingly fat manicurist
就是想杀了我
is, like, literally trying to kill me.
嗨 小贱人们 哇 瞧瞧这对波波
Hey, bitches. Whoo! Look who's working the puppies today!
你不需要一个同志老公
You don't need a gay husband...
你就是我的同志老公
'Cause you're my gay husband.
哇 我不懂这行不行
Aw. I don't really understand how that works,
但这是我听过最贴心的话了
but it's the sweetest thing anyone's ever said to me.
-不客气 -我要分手
- You're welcome. - I gotta break up with him.
-直接甩 -把计划改到周三
- Peter-out. - Move your plans to Wednesday.
-直接甩是唯一的办法 -那最简单的办法
- Peter-out's your only option. - That's the easiest way to do it.
是一周中最不可能滚床单的日
It's the least sexual night of the...
嗨 德瑞克 是我 听好
Hey, Derrick. It's me. Listen.
我想我们不适合 我理解
I don't think we should be friends anymore. I understand,
但这对我们都好 再见
but it's for the best. Good-bye.
哇 谈话有用
Wow. The conversation really works.
是啊 戴夫 有用
Yeah, Dave, it does.
嘿 我和她
You know what? This...
今天就断  - 表演
Ends today.- drama
嗨 安卓拉
Hi. Un-drea.
安卓拉
Un-drea.
刚我就 没什么
That's what I... Never mind.
听着 嗯
Listen, um...
我们需要谈一次
We need to have a conversation.
怎么了? 哦
What's up? Oh.
嗨 妈妈 什么?
Hey, mom. What?
我的天! 不
Oh, my God! No.
内莉奶奶很慈祥
Mee-Maw Nellie was such a kind soul.
她总是给小孩子们
She always carried butterscotch candies around...
带奶油糖吃
For the grandkids.
我知道你一定可以的
I know... I know you can do this.
挺住 好吧
No, you can... you can do it. Okay.
呃
Uh... Ahem.
"我记得当我还是个穿碎花裙的
"I remember one day when I was a little girl
小姑娘" 噢 你知道么
in my favorite polka dot dress..." Oh, you know what?
我做不了 安卓拉 对不起
I can't... I can't do this. Un-drea, I'm sorry,
一秒钟前你还只是戳戳我鼻子
but one minute you're booping me on the nose,
下一秒我就在你外婆的葬礼上
and the next thing I know, I'm giving the eulogy
读悼词了
at your grandma's funeral.
插一句 请大家节哀
I'm sorry for your loss, by the way.
我晕了 每次我想分手
I don't know. I tried to Peter it out,
像丹 库克的事情就发生了
and... and then there was this whole Dane cook thing,
每次我想走
but every time I tried to get away,
你就把我拉回来了
you'd just pull me back in.
你开玩笑吧?我拉你?
Are you kidding? I pulled you in?
我要的不过是玩玩 但你
All I wanted was a fun hookup, but then, you, like,
才走了二十分钟就打我电话
called me 20 minutes after you left my place,
然后昨天基本上你就求我跟你同居了
and then yesterday you basically asked me to move in
我们才认识了一周半
after a week and a half.
好吧 我想这真不是好地方
Okay, I don't think this is really the place
去争论这样的问题
to talk about this kind of thing.
我同意
I just went along with it
就因为我不要这样的谈话
because I didn't wanna have the conversation.
谈话蠢极了
The conversation sucks.
何止蠢 听好 戴夫
It blows. Listen, Dave,
你真是个好人 好吗
you're a really nice guy, okay?
但我想我们应该见见其他人
But... I think we should see other people.
好的 那我走了 不好意思
Okay. Well, I'm outta here. Sorry.
别在意 妞沙
Don't apologize. Chick-sand.
是呀
Yeah.
我戳
Boop.
好吧 希望这是最后一个了
Okay, hopefully, this is the last of them.
为什么她要把摄像头放在
I mean, why would she put a camera
冰箱底层?
on the bottom shelf of the fridge anyway?
我可不知道 偷窥狂都很神经
I don't know. Peeps are into some weird stuff.
而且你春光乍泄
Plus, you tend to show a lot of cleave
当你往保鲜格里拿东西的的时候
when you reach for the crisper.
哦 真恶心 我上周好像抄了三次菜
Oh, gross. I made, like, three stir-frys last week.
你都觉得有问题了 那绝对有问题
Man, when your gut's wrong, it's really wrong.
至少现在都搞定了
At least it all worked out.
你皮厚着呢
I wouldn't go so far...
八千美元?
$8,000?
结果证明我在上周的辣妹室友网
Turns out last week when I was on smokinhotroomies.com...
我点击率第一
I got the most hits ever.
哇哦
Wow. Yep.
-是真的钱 -嗯
That's real money. Mm-hmm.
好吧 把它放回冰箱去 不要穿胸罩
Okay. Put this thing back in the fridge, take your bra off,
-我们来做沙拉 -什么?
- and let's make a salad. - What?